Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
higher in protein and way lower in
calories. This is American Dream. One of
the most requested flavors I've gotten
so far. Let me show you how to make it.
To start, you're going to need a vanilla
protein shake. And then you're going to
add some sweetener, salt, zantham gum,
vanilla bean paste. And then you're
going to blend that all together. Throw
it in the freezer and let it sit there
for at least 16 hours. Once it is
completely frozen, you can take it out
and run under hot water for about a
minute and then throw it in your Ninja
Creamy on the light ice cream setting.
It'll probably come out a little bit
powdery like mine did. But if so, you
can just scrape down the sides with a
butter knife and then throw back in the
creamy on the re-spin setting. After
that spin, it should come out looking
beautiful. Nice and creamy, rich,
smooth. So, we're going to smooth out
the top and then top it with whatever
chocolate fil waffle cone pieces you can
find. I found these ones from Muddy
Bites. They're all pretty much the same,
so don't worry about the brand too much.
Just use whatever you can find. And then
top it with some caramel sauce, and you
are good to go.